
const questions = [
    {
      question: "What is Hawking's attitude when he answered the questions, 'How do you feel about having ALS'?",
      options: ["Negative",  "Positive" ,  "Neutral", "Sickening"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "The doctors",
      options: ["told Hawking that he would recover very soon", "were able to treat about Hawking's condition", "told Hawking that he had multiple sclerosis", "could give only vitamins to Hawking"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following activities did Stephan Hawking enjoy doing",
      options: ["chess", "rowing", "painting"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "He chose to pursue theoretical physics,as that would",
      options: ["Need his presence constantly in the laboratory", "Not need this presence constantly in the laboratory", "His condition would be unsupportive for any other area"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "The science of the origin development of the universe is called",
      options: ["astrology", "cosmology", "universology"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "When Stephan Hawking says he had trouble in getting accomodation he meant.",
      options: ["college admission", "hostel room", "housing"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "The word that means coming up with a new theory is",
      options: ["pound", "propound", "produce"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Hawking chose to work in theoretical physics because",
      options: ["he was good only in it", "he got a research fellowship to work in theoretical physics", "his condition would not come in his way in doing research in theoretical physics", "his family wanted him to choose"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Tracheostomy operation",
      options: ["improved Hawking's speech", "made Hawking lose the ability to speech completely", "made Hawking's speech slurred", "did not make any changes to his speech"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "Hawking's life story tells us that",
      options: ["he led a very happy life", "he led a very sad life", "one need not lose hope how worse the situation may be", "one should accept it as fate"],
      answer: 2
    }, ];

 export default questions;